Madalina Martiniuc

Strada Principala 127Darmanesti, Suceava | +40750802090 | mmartiniuc7@gmail.com

Summary

My name is Madalina Martiniuc, I am a student in the last year at the University of Computer Science in Turin.

I have lived most of my life in Italy, from when I was 10 years old and did all of my studies there. I've always been passionate about computers and programming. My new goal is to learn as much as possible and take part in different projects. I have knowledge of all kinds of programming languages but I am mostly interested in the front-end part.

Education

UNIVERSITY OF TURIN, COMPUTER SCIENCE, TURIN

I have attended courses that cover everything related to computer science such as algorithms, data structures, databases and courses on different programming languages such as Java. I have also attended courses on front end development that included HTML5, CSS3, Javascript and Jquery basics.

Work Experience

JUST PLUS: JUNIOR WEB DEVELOPER - 1/08/2022- CURRENT

During my time at Just Plus, I have worked with different technologies, but mostly HTML5, CSS3 (and Bootstrap), Javascript and Jquery. I worked on building different responsive websites using my knowledge on these technologies but also using new ones such as Elementor and Wordpress Gutenberg Blocks.

For the backend part, I have mostly worked with PHP and personalized Wordpress themes or created different functions.

Internships

OSF - 1/02/2022- 1/03/2022

It was a month long internship in which we had to re-create an eccomerce website using only HTML5, CSS3, Javascript/Jquery. I had the opportunity to learn and use SCSS. I was provided with FSD files for the project with the requirements and the design and had to use my skills on avocode and photoshop.

Link: https://osf-madalina-martiniuc.netlify.app/

ASSIST SOFTWARE: TECH CHALLENGE - 25/02/2022- 18/03/2022

During this 2 week challenge, the participants were divided in teams of 4 and had to create a full stack office space management website. I participated as a front end developer and using my React skills created the website following the design project on Figma.

Github repo: https://github.com/madalinamart/tech-challenge

Languages

Romanian: nativeItalian: native

- English: advanced